{
    "id": "baa4e43563cb45c5a1a7134508d4689e",
    "title": "Too, too much or too many",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9ce6e97a5020462ab8ba181dc68a1f7f",
            "title": "Too, Too Much Or Too Many",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He is …………….. old to work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too much",
                        "too many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is ………………. cold to go out now.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too much",
                        "too many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There was ……………….. snow to go walking. (",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too many",
                        "too much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You put ………………… salt in the soup.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too many",
                        "too much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I put down the box because it was ………………. heavy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too much",
                        "too many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He does not like women who are …………….. tall.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too much",
                        "too many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I cannot solve this problem – it’s ………………… difficult.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too much",
                        "too many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have got ………………… work to do.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too much",
                        "too many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You have eaten ..................... rice.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too much",
                        "too many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ask ...................... questions.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too many",
                        "too much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}